Ganta Mohan

Freelancer & Full Stack Developer

\(+91-961885656

antamohan.556@gmail.com

☐ Portfolio ☐ LinkedIn





About Me

As a Full Stack Developer, I am excited to announce that I am actively seeking new opportunities to grow and advance my career. With 1.5+ years of experience in developing and maintaining web applications and software systems, I am confident in my ability to contribute to the success of any organization.

Certifications

- Java Certificate @ HackerRank
- SQL (Advanced) Certificate @ HackerRank
- Java Explorer @ Oracle
- Python @ HackerRank
- Python 101 for Data Science @IBM

谷 Skills

- AWS
- JAVA
- PYTHON
- DJANGO
- MERN STACK
- DATA SCINCE
- SQL

At LINKS

- https://github.com/Mohan-Ganta
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/mo han-ganta/



Education

B-Tech(2020 -2024) **SWARNANDHRA COLLEGE OF ENGINEERING &** TECHNOLOGY, NARASAPUR. PIN -534275 (CC-A2) computer science engineering



Experience

Vitha Learning (Dec-2021 - Present) **FULL STACK DEVELOPER**

- created more than 500+ web pages
- Designed and implemented efficient database schemas, ensuring seamless storage and retrieval of data.
- AWS,GIT,GTHUB,MERN,PYTHON,DJANGO

DPI Rainbow Foundation Internship (Feb 2023 - Mar 2023) **FULL STACK DEVELOPER**

- Maintaining SQL Database
- Hosting and Deploy with domine names

CodingZen (Oct 2021 - Nov 2021) PROJECT TEAM LEAD (MACHINE LEARNING)

• At the Live Project on 50 Startups, I am a Project Lead. Python-based machine learning for data analysis and Twitter sentiment analysis